As times change, difficult cases will increase in number!
تتضاعف القضايا المعقّدة مع مضيّ خط الوقت
Today's stage is a library at night!
!مسرح اليوم هو مكتبة في الليل
Its books smell of crime!
!تفوح من كتبها رائحة جريمة
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
Hattori Heiji showed up, and then I drank his alcohol...
...ظهر هاتّوري هيجي، وشربتُ الساكي الذي جلبه
That's gotta be it!
!لا شكّ في الأمر
Drinking that alcohol turned me back to normal!
!رجعتُ لطبيعتي بشربي لذاك الساكي
If I drink this all, I can turn back completely!
!إذا شربتُ هذا كلّه سأعود لطبيعتي كليّاً
Hey, you!
!ولد
You know you shouldn't drink alcohol!
لا يمكن للصغار شرب ساكي، تعرف ذلك
Your friends are here!
أتى أصدقاؤك
Once I drink that alcohol and turn back into a high school student,
بعدما أشرب ذاك الساكي وأرجع ،طالباً في المدرسة الثانوية
I might never get to hang out with them again...
قد لن أستطيع التسكّع معهم هكذا مُجدداً
Beika Library
مكتبة بيكا
Geez, they're all such lame books...
...يا إلهي، كلّها كتب سخيفة
I'm supposed to do a book report on this?
يُفترض بي كتابة تقرير لهذه؟
And what's with this awkward arrangement?!
وما خطب هذا الترتيب الغريب؟
Well, guess it can't be helped.
ليس باليد حيلة، فهذا ركن الأطفال
This is the children's section and all...
لا بد أنّهم يعبثون به
An imported foreign book...
...كتاب مستورد أجنبيّ
Huh? It's shrink-wrapped in its case backwards...
...ماذا؟ إنّه مغلف في غطائه عكسياً
Now, now. This isn't a book for children.
هذا ليس كتاباً صالحاً للأطفال
Conan-kun! Look! Police cars!
!كونان-كن، انظر! سيّارات شرطة
Eh?!
ماذا؟
What do you suppose happened?
أوقع أمرٌ ما؟
Maybe it's a case!
!ربما هناك قضيّة
Used Books
كتب مستعملة
Sir! There are policemen downstairs!
سيّدي، يوجد رجال شرطة في الأسفل
Eh? Oh, I see. I'll be right there.
ماذا؟ حسناً، سآتي فوراً
I'm gonna check it out!
!سأذهب للتفقد
Hold the elevator!
!أوقفوا المصعد قليلاً
Max Capacity: 7 people, 450 kg
السعة القصوى: 7 أشخاص، 450 كغ
We're over the passenger limit.
تجاوزنا حدّ الصاعدين
Maximum capacity is seven people.
السعة القصوى 7 أشخاص
One!
!واحد
Two! Three! Four! Five! Six! Seven!
!اثنان! ثلاثة! أربعة !خمسة! ستة! سبعة
There's only seven people in here!
!يوجد سبعة فحسب هنا
You didn't count yourself!
!لم تحسب نفسك
Told you! Genta-kun doesn't catch colds--
...أخبرتكم! لن يُصاب غينتا-كن بالزكام
Quiet!
!اسكت
No choice! Let's take the stairs!
!ليس أمامنا خيار، لننزل من الأدراج
You're the director of this library, yes?
أنت مدير هذه المكتبة، صحيح؟
Yes. My name is Tsugawa.
أجل، أُدعى تسوغاوا
I'm here about this fellow,
أتيتُ بخصوص هذا الرجل
a librarian named Tamada Kazuo-san.
أمين مكتبة يُدعى تامادا كازو-سان
Oh, yes. He's been taking unapproved leave since yesterday.
أجل، أخذ إجازةً غير مصرحة منذ الأمس
Hey, Inspector! What's going on?
حضرة المفتّش! أحدث أمرٌ ما؟
Did something happen to him?
أحلّ أمرٌ به؟
Actually, Tamada-san has been missing since two nights ago.
في الواقع، تامادا-سان مفقود منذ ليلتين
Eh?! Y-You can't be serious!
...ماذا؟ لا-لا يمكن
I hear he worked overtime with you two nights ago...
سمعت أنّه عمل معك بدوام إضافيّ قبل ليلتين
Yes...
...أ-أجل
But I left before he did,
لكنّي غادرت قبله
so I'm not sure what happened afterward...
فلا أدري ما حصل بعدها
Say, then why are you checking the library's storeroom?
لمَ تتفقدون مخزن المكتبة إذاً؟
He might've been abducted on his way home, you know.
ربما اُختطف في طريق عودته
It's just to be on the safe side.
هذا من باب الحيطة
Tamada-san is a meticulous person;
فتامادا-سان شخص دقيق جداً
he always called his wife
يتّصل بزوجته من المكتبة
from this library before leaving for home.
قبل رجوعه دوماً
But he didn't two nights ago.
لكنه لم يفعل ذلك قبل ليلتين
In short, he was either taken away,
ما يعني أنّ أحداً أخذه من هنا
or is still inside this library.
أو لا يزال في المكتبة
But if he is here,
لكن إذا كان هنا
then there's a good chance he's already been killed!
!فيُحتمل جدّاً أنّه قُتل بالفعل
Inspector. We checked all inconspicuous places,
،سيّدي المفتش، فتّشنا في كلّ الأماكن الخفية
but found nothing...
لكن لم نجد شيئاً
I guess that means he left...
...لعلّه غادر بالفعل إذاً
Alright! Let's go!
!حسناً، سنرحل
I apologize for the inconvenience!
نعتذر على الإزعاج
Not at all...
...لا-لا مشكلة
Alright! Everyone's gone!
!حسناً، ذهب الجميع
Geez, I told you to go home!
!يا إلهي، أخبرتكم بالعودة
What now, Conan-kun?!
ماذا سنفعل الآن يا كونان-كن؟
We find the body.
نجد الجثّة
Eh?! But the police said...
...ماذا؟ لكنّ الشرطة قالت
Something stinks about this library...
هناك أمرٌ نتن بشأن هذه المكتبة
Stinks?
نتن؟
The elevator! Someone's coming up!
!المصعد! أحدهم يصعد
Hide!
!اختبئوا
That's Tsugawa-san, the library director!
!إنّه... مدير المكتبة تسوغاوا-سان
What's he up to at this hour?
ماذا يفعل في هذا الوقت؟
That's where that weird foreign book was...
...هناك حيث كان الكتاب الأجنبيّ الغريب
Tamada was such a fool.
كان تامادا ساذجاً بحقّ
If only he hadn't looked inside this,
لم يكن ليمت
he wouldn't have had to die.
لو لم ينظر داخل هذا
And the police are the police.
والشرطة تبقى الشرطة
They left so easily...
غادروا بكلّ سهولة
Little did they know Tamada is resting inside this very library...
لم يعلموا أنّ تامادا راقد في هذه المكتبة
Just as I thought!
!كما ظننت
Tamada-san's body is inside this library!
جثّة تامادا-سان موجودة !في هذه المكتبة بالفعل
And it was the library director who killed him!
!ومن قتله هو المدير تسوغاوا
But where is the body?
لكن أين الجثّة؟
That's the weird book that was shrink-wrapped backwards in its case...
...ذاك الكتاب الغريب الذي كان مغلّفاً عكسياً
It's too dark to see anything!
...لا أرى شيئاً من الظلام
Who's there?!
!من هناك؟
Is someone there?!
!أيوجد أحد؟
In here?!
!هنا؟
I don't think we should leave for a while...
...لا أظنّ أن علينا المغادرة من هنا لفترة
C'mon, Conan, I'm hungry. I want an eel boxed lunch...
...أشعر بالجوع يا كونان، أريد أكل غداء أنقليس معلّب
Alright! He's gone!
حسناً، غادر
I'll start with the strange books in that box...
سأبدأ بالكتب الغريبة في ذاك الصندوق
Huh? They're empty!
!ماذا؟ إنّها فارغة
He must've put the contents in his bag before he left!
لعلّه وضع المحتويات في حقيبته قبل مغادرته
I doubt it.
يستحيل ذلك
Look at all these cases!
انظر لكلّ هذه الأغطية
His bag couldn't have fit it all!
لا يمكن أن تتسع حقيبته لكلّ هذا
The ones he couldn't fit,
لا بدّ أنّه خبأ
he must've hid somewhere in this room.
ما لم يستطع أخذه في مكان ما بهذه الغرفة
Looks like we'll hafta look for the books before we look for the body.
يبدو أنّ علينا البحث عن تلك الكتب قبل الجثّة
So it's finally time for the Junior Detective League to do its stuff?!
!حان وقت فرقة فتيان التحرّي أخيراً إذاً؟
Y-Yeah...
...أ-أجل
Let's start with this bookcase!
لنبدأ بهذه الخزانة أوّلاً
Let's split up and check both sides!
لننفصل ونتفقد كلا الجانبين
Alright!
!أجل
I-Idiot! Don't turn the lights on!
!حـ-حمقى! لا تضيئوا الأنوار
But it was dark...
...لكنّ المكان مظلم
What if he sees?!
!ماذا لو رآنا؟
Don't worry!
لا تقلق
I'm sure he's already long gone!
!لا بدّ أنّه غادر بالفعل
I sure hope so...
...آمل ذلك
Looks like he's really gone...
...يبدو أنّه غادر حقاً
Any strange books?
وجدت أيّ كتب غريبة؟
Nope, nothing.
كلا، مطلقاً
Looks like they're not in this bookcase.
يبدو أنّها ليست في هذه الخزانة
We took out most of the books.
فقد أخرجنا معظم الكتب
What the--?! They haven't taken any of their books out!
!ماذا؟ لم يخرجا أيّاً من كتبهما
Hey! Genta!
!أنت! غينتا
Oh, Conan-kun...
...كونان-كن
What're you guys doing?!
ما الذي تفعلانه؟
We took out all our books!
!أخرجنا كلّ كتبنا
That's strange!
!هذا غريب
We took all ours out, too!
!أخرجنا كلّ كتبنا أيضاً
W-What's with this book!?
ما-ما خطب هذا الكتاب؟
There's no spine!
!لا ظهر له
You're right!
معك حق
H-Hey! All these books are like that!
ا-انظروا، كلّ الكتب هنا كذلك
I get it! These books weren't backwards in their cases;
فهمت، لم تكن هذه الكتب مقلوبةً في أغطيتها
they never had spines to begin with!
!لم تكن لها أظهر من البداية
Eh? What do you mean?
ماذا؟ ما قصدك؟
Basically, the director put these books
أي أنّ المدير وضع هذه الكتب
between the ones on the shelves
بين الكتب على الرّفوف
to make three rows.
لصنع ثلاثة صفوف
So if someone took out a book,
،لذا إن أخذ أحد كتاباً
they would see open pages behind it.
سيرى صفحات مفتوحة وراءه
They would think it's a book on the other side,
سيظنّها كتاباً على الجانب الآخر، ولن يدرك الحقيقة
and not realize the truth.
هذا ركن الأطفال، مما يجعل الأمر أسهل تصديقاً
The books were all skewed because the middle books pushed them.
كانت الكتب غير مرتبة لأنّ الكتب في المنتصف دفعتها عند إعادة أحد لكتاب
But why do that?
لكن لمَ قد يفعل ذلك؟
The fact these weird books are imported from overseas
...كون هذه الكتب الغريبة مستوردة من خارج البلاد
probably means they contain guns, or...
...يعني أنّ محتواها غالباً مسدّسات، أو
...drugs!
!مخدّرات
T-There's some in here, too!
!يـ-يوجد هنا أيضاً
And here!
!وهنا
So basically, that library director is smuggling drugs?!
أي أنّ ذاك المدير يهرّب المخدّرات؟
Yeah. He would store the drugs here,
أجل، يخزّنها هنا
and then sell them off slowly.
ثم يبيعها ببطء
Tamada-san probably discovered this,
تامادا-سان اكتشف ذلك صدفةً غالباً
and was killed.
وقُتل كيلا يفضح الأمر
By Director Tsugawa...
على يد المدير تسوغاوا
Huh? That's strange. I can't get through...
ماذا؟ هذا غريب، لا يتّصل الخط
Is it out of order?
أهو معطل؟
Yeah. Our only option now is to leave and tell the police directly.
أجل، خيارنا الوحيد هو الخروج وإخبار الشرطة مباشرةً
Then let's find the body too while we're at it!
!لنجد الجثّة بينما نفعل ذلك إذاً
Yeah! Good thinking! That'll double our achievement!
!أجل! فكرة حسنة، هكذا سيتضاعف إنجازنا
I agree!
!أتّفق
Oh, geez...
...أنتم
Once we find the body, we'll be so famous!
سينتشر اسمنا مجدداً بعدما نجد الجثّة
This is so exciting!
!هذا مُثير
My shoe came untied...
...انفك رباط حذائي
It's hard to tie it in the dark...
...من الصعب ربطه في الظلام
Ayumi-chan!
!أيومي-تشان
What're you doing?!
ما الذي تفعلينه؟
My shoe...
...حذائي
That's what you get for wearing those annoying shoes!
هذا ما يحصل لارتداءك حذاءً مزعجاً
You're mean!
!يا لقسوتك
These are my favorite ones, you know!
!هذا حذائي المفضل
I guess nobody would hide a body in a bookcase, huh?
لن يخبّئ أحد جثّةً في خزانة كتب في العادة، صحيح؟
But the police did say they searched all inconspicuous places!
!لكنّ الشرطة قالت أنّها فتّشت كل الأماكن الخفية
There's no place left to look...
لم تبق أماكن نبحث فيها
Hey! There are weird bookcases in the back!
!اسمعوا، توجد خزانات كتب غريبة في الخلف
See?! They got weird handles!
!انظروا! لديها مقابض غريبة
Oh! These are mobile bookcases!
هذه خزانات كتب متنقلة
Mobile?
متنقلة؟
Yes!
أجل
Turn this handle, and... See?
تدير المقبض هكذا و... انظروا
Awesome!
!مُذهل
I dunno... It would be easy for someone to discover the body here...
لا يُعقل... سيكون سهلاً أن يكتشف أحد الجثة إنّ خبأها هنا
This is fun!
!هذا مُسلٍّ
What's wrong, Genta?
ما الخطب يا غينتا؟
Darn it!
!تبّاً
The handle's too hard to turn!
!المقبض متصلّب ولا أستطيع تحريكه
It couldn't be!
!أيمكن؟
Mitsuhiko! Ayumi-chan! Help me move this!
!ميتسوهيكو! أيومي-تشان! ساعداني بتحريك هذه
Okay!
حسناً
Ready... go!
...استعداد
Huh? There's nothing here...
...ماذا؟ لا شيء هنا
And there's nothing strange here...
ولا شيء غريب بالتحديد
Which means the reason it wouldn't move...
...ما يعني أنّ سبب صعوبة تحريكها
...was because you're heavy, Genta!
!هو ثقلك أنت يا غينتا
W-Well, excuse me!
!غـ-غلطتي أنا
You're too fat, Genta-kun!
!أنت بدين جدّاً يا غينتا-كن
How much do you weigh?!
كم وزنك؟
F-Forty kilograms!
!أ-أربعون كيلو
That's exactly twice my weight!
!هذا ضعف وزني
Man, I can't stand this...
...يا إلهي، لا أستطيع تحمل هذا
Just endure it! Today's my last day hanging out with these kids!
اصبر! هذا آخر يوم سأتسكع فيه !مع هؤلاء الأطفال
Once I drink that alcohol and return to being a high schooler...
بعدما أشرب ذاك الساكي وأرجع ...لكوني طالباً في الثانوية
Return?
أرجع؟
I'm only 15 kilograms! You need to diet more!
!وزني 15 كيلو، عليك القيام بحمية
S-Shut up!
!ا-اصمتي
Oh, yeah! I forgot! I'm a kid now!
!صحيح، نسيت! أنا طفل الآن
Hold on! I was 18 kg when I last weighed myself!
لحظة، كان وزني 18 كغ عندما قسته آخر مرة
Hold the elevator!
!أوقفوا المصعد قليلاً
I know where the body is hidden!
!عرفت أين خبّأ الجثة
Hey, Conan! Wait up!
!كونان! انتظرنا
Hey, Conan! Where are you?!
كونان، أين أنت؟
Conan-kun! Say something!
!كونان-كن، قل شيئاً
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Where were you?!
أين كنت؟
Just up in the machinery room.
في غرفة المكائن في الأعلى
Was the body in there?!
أكانت الجثّة هناك؟
No, I only went there to switch these elevator doors to manual.
كلا، ذهبتُ لتبديل تحكّم باب المصعد للوضع اليدوي لا أكثر
The body... is probably in here!
!الجثّة غالباً... هنا
You're sure it's in here?
أأنت متأكد أنّها هنا؟
Yep.
أجل
The proof is the overload buzzer that went off
والدليل هو إنذار الطنّان
when we all got on the elevator this afternoon.
عندما دخلنا المصعد ظهيرة اليوم
Eh?
ماذا؟
Of course it went off;
لكنّه تفعّل لأنّ عددنا
there were 8 people in the elevator...
كان أكثر من 8 في المصعد
Don't be stupid! We're kids!
!أحمق، نحن أطفال
All together, we weigh at most 100 kg!
!نزن مجتمعين 100 كغ على الأكثر
An adult and a half!
!بالغ ونصف
Even with the weight of the adults and the box,
،حتّى مع وزن البالغين والصندوق
there was one whole person missing for the buzzer to go off!
!كان هناك شخص ناقص ليتم تفعيل الإنذار
Yes. Someone was riding this elevator from the very start.
أجل، كان هناك شخص على المصعد من البداية
Somewhere where nobody could see him...
...في مكان لا يمكن أن يراه فيه أحد
...on the roof!
!فوق المصعد
It would seem he was thrown down this shaft after being strangled.
يبدو أنّه رُمي من الأعلى فوق المصعد بعدما خُنق بالنظر لحالته
It was all Director Tsugawa's doing.
كان كلّ ذلك من فعل المدير تسوغاوا
Now let's go tell the police!
!حسناً، لنذهب لإخبار الشرطة
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
T-Tsu--
...تسو-تسو
D-Dir--
...مد-مد
Atsudir?
تسومد؟
D-Director Tsugawa!
!المدير تسوغاوا
What are you kiddos doing here at this hour?
ماذا تفعلون في هذا الوقت يا صغار؟
Let's all leave together...
سنرجع معاً
Come...
...هيّا
Listen. Do exactly as I say.
اسمعوا، افعلوا ما سأقوله لكم
What are you discussing?
ما الذي تتكلمون فيه؟
Let's leave now...
لنرجع معاً
Don't underestimate us just because we're kids, Director!
لا تستهن بنا لأنّنا أطفال فحسب أيّها المدير
What?
ماذا؟
We've got the evidence.
لدينا الدليل
The bookcase trick, the hidden drugs,
،حيلة خزانة الكتب، المخدرات المخبأة
and the fact you killed Tamada-san after he found out!
!وقتلك تامادا-سان بعدما اكتشف أمرك
Who... Who are you?!
!من... من أنت؟
Edogawa Conan! A detective!
!إيدوغاوا كونان! مُتحرٍّ
D-Detective?!
!مـ-متحرٍّ؟
Oh, no, you don't!
!لن أدعك
He slides, he's safe!
!انزلاق آمن
We did it!
!فعلناها
Damn you brats! You can't escape me!
!أيّها الأوغاد، لن تهربوا أيّها الأطفال اللعينون
I made it!
وصلتُ في الوقت
It's time to die...
...استعدوا
...brats!
...أيّها الأطفال
T-They're gone? Did they get off?
اختفوا؟ هل نزلوا في منتصف الطريق؟
No matter. With the elevator off,
،حسناً، لا يهم. بعدما أوقفت المصعد
they're trapped like rats...
سيصبحون محتجزين كالجرذان
Just you wait, little rats.
انتظري أيّتها الجرذان الصغيرة
I'll kill each and every one of you!
!سأقتلكم واحداً تلو الآخر
Hey! Where are you, kiddos?!
!أين أنتم يا صغار؟
I'm sorry about earlier!
!أعتذر على ما فعلتُه قبل قليل
I won't try to hurt you now! Come on out!
!لن أحاول أذيّتكم مُجدداً! اخرجوا فحسب
In here?
هنا؟
Do they honestly think this is a barricade?
أظنّوا أن هذا حاجز حقاً؟
It's leaning...
...إنّه مائل
Ah! They stuck books under it...
فهمت، وضعوا كتباً تحته
Now!
!الآن
Kids have such shallow cleverness.
للأطفال حيل سطحية
Don't worry. You won't be lonely...
لا تقلقوا، لن تشعروا بالوحدة
Because I'm about to send all four of you to the afterlife!
!لأنّي سأرسلكم الأربعة للعالم الآخر معاً
We did it!
!نجحنا
It worked perfectly!
!عملت بإتقان
After our call, the police rushed over and arrested Director Tsugawa.
بعد بلاغنا، أسرعت الشرطة للمكان واعتقلت المدير تسوغاوا
They also recovered Tamada-san's body and all the drugs.
استرجعوا أيضاً جثّة تامادا-سان وكلّ المخدرات
And so Edogawa Conan's final case came to an end.
وهكذا أُقفلت آخر قضيّة لإيدوغاوا كونان
That was so scary!
!كان ذلك مخيفاً
I thought we were goners!
!ظننتنا هالكين
Get real! Good always wins!
!أحمق! الخير ينتصر دوماً
So now it's goodbye to this body...
...يمكنني توديع هذا الجسد الآن
Let's do that again sometime, Conan-kun!
!لنعاود الكرّة في وقت ما يا كونان-كن
The detective club!
!فرقة فتيان التحرّي
Together, the four of us can solve any case easily!
!يمكننا الأربعة معاً حلّ أيّ قضية بسهولة
Alright! Let's try hard next time, too!
!حسناً! لنجتهد المرة القادمة أيضاً
Yeah!
!أجل
And... goodbye to them, too...
و... توديعهم أيضاً
C-Conan-kun?
كونان-كن؟
See you!
!وداعاً
It's like he's leaving somehow...
...أشعر أنّه يرحل بشكلٍ ما
Yeah...
أجل
That's right! I'm turning back into my normal body!
!صحيح، سأرجع لجسدي الطبيعيّ
Into high school student, Kudo Shinichi!
!لطالب المرحلة الثانوية، كودو شينتشي
With this alcohol... I can finally be me again!
!يمكنني العودة أخيراً... بهذا الساكي
Conan-kun? Did you just get home?
كونان-كن؟ أرجعت الآن؟
What were you doing this late at--
...ماذا كنت تفعل حتّى هذا الوقت
Conan-kun?
كونان-كن؟
What?! Your body reverted?!
!ماذا؟! رجع جسدك لطبيعته؟
Yeah! After one drink of this alcohol!
!أجل، بعد جرعة واحدة من هذا الساكي
You can't be serious...
...لا يُعقل
If you don't believe me, then just watch!
!إذا ظننتني أكذب فراقب
H-Hey!
!ا-انتظر
Here it comes! My body's warming up!
!ها هو! أشعر بجسدي يسخن
C'mon, Doc! I haven't turned back one bit!
!بروفسور! لم أرجع البتّة
Immunity?
مناعة؟
Basically, the alcohol somehow turned you back the first time,
أي أنّ الساكي أعاد جسدك لطبيعته ...بدايةً بشكلٍ ما
but your body started to produce a substance to counteract the alcohol,
،لكنّ كوّن جسدك بعدها مادةً لمقاومة الساكي
thus rendering it ineffective.
فمنع فعاليته
Yeah, right! I just haven't had enough yet!
!لا تمازحني! لم أشرب ما يكفي فحسب حتماً
H-Hey, stop it, Shinichi!
!انتظر! توقف يا شينتشي
Gulp, gulp!
!مزيداً مزيداً
Stop it!
!توقف
What's wrong, Conan-kun?!
ما الخطب يا كونان-كن؟
You don't look so good...
...تبدو شاحباً
Is it another cold?
أهو الزكام مجدداً؟
Don't be dumb. It's just a hangover...
...يا حمقى، إنّه مجرد أثر شراب
Another miss?
إخفاق آخر؟
Twenty in a row...
...عشرون توالياً
He sure sucks at golf...
إنّه سيّئ في الغولف حقاً
Yeah, he says he's not good at any sports that use equipment.
أجل، قال أنّه لا يجيد أيّ رياضة بها أدوات
Then what was that metallic sound?!
ما كان ذاك الصوت المعدني إذاً؟
That's it!
!فهمت
This is a trick the killer set!
!هذه حيلة وضعها القاتل
That person definitely did it!
!إنّه ذاك الشخص بلا شك
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Golf Range Murder Case."
جريمة قتل ساحة تمرين الغولف
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Driver and Ball.
مجموعة غولف
You won't want to miss what dad does next episode.
،الحلقة القادمة لا يمكن تفويتها !حتّى للآباء
And Genta's detective work is a nice shot.
!استنتاج غينتا أشبه بضربة جميلة
That's out of bounds.
خارج الملعب